[
    {
        "question": "Nafsina touched my hand with love",
        "words": {
          "4": "Nafsina",
          "1": "hand",
          "3": "love",
          "2": "been",
          "5": "my",
          "6": "by",
          "7": "with",
          "8": "touched",
          "9": "being",
          "10": "was"
        },
        "answers":[[5,1,10,8,6,4,7,3]]
    },
    {
        "question": "I told you these words before",
        "words": {
          "4": "words",
          "1": "before",
          "3": "had",
          "2": "by",
          "5": "told",
          "6": "these",
          "7": "you",
          "8": "me",
          "9": "were",
          "10": "been",
          "11": "to"
        },
        "answers":[[6,4,9,5,11,7,2,8,1]]
    },
    {
        "question": "My father was driving a car very fast",
        "words": {
          "4": "father",
          "1": "fast",
          "3": "being",
          "2": "was",
          "5": "a",
          "6": "being",
          "7": "been",
          "8": "car",
          "9": "very",
          "10": "my",
          "11": "driven",
          "12": "by"
        },
        "answers":[[5,8,2,6,11,9,1,12,10,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Paritosh was cheating us lot of money",
        "words": {
          "4": "Paritosh",
          "1": "lot",
          "3": "cheated",
          "2": "we",
          "5": "been",
          "6": "by",
          "7": "were",
          "8": "money",
          "9": "being",
          "10": "was",
          "11": "of"
        },
        "answers":[[2,7,9,3,1,11,8,6,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "We were having lunch at that time",
        "words": {
          "4": "had",
          "1": "that",
          "3": "us",
          "2": "been",
          "5": "lunch",
          "6": "by",
          "7": "being",
          "8": "at",
          "9": "was",
          "10": "time"
        },
        "answers":[[5,9,7,4,6,3,8,1,10]]
    },
    {
        "question": "I shall not give you any trouble",
        "words": {
          "4": "given",
          "1": "me",
          "3": "be",
          "2": "you",
          "5": "any",
          "6": "by",
          "7": "not",
          "8": "being",
          "9": "trouble",
          "10": "will"
        },
        "answers":[[2,10,7,3,4,5,9,6,1]]
    },
    {
        "question": "I shall go to the market",
        "words": {
          "4": "market",
          "1": "by",
          "3": "gone",
          "2": "to",
          "5": "was",
          "6": "me"
        },
        "answers":[[]]
    },
    {
        "question": "He only would know the meaning of love",
        "words": {
          "4": "meaning",
          "1": "knew",
          "3": "him",
          "2": "would",
          "5": "the",
          "6": "be",
          "7": "known",
          "8": "only",
          "9": "love",
          "10": "to",
          "11": "of"
        },
        "answers":[[5,4,11,9,2,6,7,10,3,8]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Guptas should not hate their neighbours",
        "words": {
          "4": "neigbours",
          "1": "be",
          "3": "Guptas",
          "2": "not",
          "5": "the",
          "6": "their",
          "7": "by",
          "8": "been",
          "9": "should",
          "10": "hated"
        },
        "answers":[[6,4,9,2,1,107,5,3]]
    },
    {
        "question": "I could be a cricketer",
        "words": {
          "4": "cricketer",
          "1": "by",
          "3": "could",
          "2": "a",
          "5": "be",
          "6": "me",
          "7": "been"
        },
        "answers":[[]]
    },
    {
        "question": "I could play cricket instead of football",
        "words": {
          "4": "played",
          "1": "football",
          "3": "been",
          "2": "cricket",
          "5": "me",
          "6": "be",
          "7": "by",
          "8": "could",
          "9": "of",
          "10": "instead"
        },
        "answers":[[2,10,9,1,8,6,4,7,5]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Martha may learn Spanish in six months",
        "words": {
          "4": "Martha",
          "1": "Spanish",
          "3": "be",
          "2": "the",
          "5": "may",
          "6": "in",
          "7": "months",
          "8": "learnt",
          "9": "six",
          "10": "by",
          "11": "learned"
        },
        "answers":[[1,5,3,8,10,4,6,9,7]]
    }
]